lovepoemsandquotes.com 2006-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Love Poems And Quotes

Love Poems And Quotes is firmly committed to the privacy of our clients. We have created this Privacy Policy to let you know under what circumstances information is collected and how this information is used. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please click here to contact us.

**1.** _Personal Data_. We retain the name and e-mail address of visitors who submit a quote or poem via our web site so that we may notify them if their submission was selected. This information is deleted at the end of each month.

**2.** _Confidentiality_. No information of ANY kind (eg: e-mail addresses) is ever shared with third parties other than that which is clearly indicated within this Privacy Policy.

**3.** _Aggregate Data_. We gather certain generic information with respect to visitors' use of our web site such as the number of unique visitors and the areas on the web site that they favor. We only look at this data on a collective basis, in summary form.

**4.** _IP Addresses_. We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. An IP address is a unique number assigned to your computer when you are browsing the internet. We log this information so that we can monitor overall traffic trends as well as the number of visitors visiting the web site. This information is used SOLELY to improve the quality of our web site.

**5.** _Cookies_. Cookies are pieces of information sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The web site analysis tool we use on our site employs the use of ‘cookies’ within our site. By tracking the information contained in the ‘cookie’, the software can calculate various aggregate statistical data. The cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information.

**6.** The Web Site Analysis Tool we use on our site (AddFreeStats) employs the use of ‘cookies’ within our site for monitoring what is referred to as ‘unique visitors’. When a visitor comes to our web site, a very small cookie is stored on his or her computer. By tracking the information contained in the ‘cookie’, the Web Site Analysis Tool can determine how many different (unique) visitors come to our web site. This ‘cookie’ does not contain any personally identifiable information.

**7.** _External Links_. On our site, we have links to other web sites that may collect personal information about you. This policy does not cover the information practices of such web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these sites as their policies may be very different.

**Click here for Page 2 of our Privacy Policy**
